原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     木浅  苏小黛  海云生  kathy567
翻译     glida  Margaery  Giggles
时间轴     西·查  噃噃  没有影子  啾
校对     布塔
后期     渔夫
总监     布塔
双子杀手
比利时  列日
六号车厢  启动了
Car number six. We are moving.
座位4A  重复  4A
4-Alpha. Repeat, 4-Alpha.
靠窗  周围都是他的人
Window seat. His team's on all sides.
收到
Copy that.
速度呢
Speed?
每小时238千米  速度稳定
Two thirty-eight kilometers per hour and holding steady.
你状态还好吗
You all right over there?
我就喜欢杀坏人
I do love capping me some bad guys.
等等  等等  有平民
Wait! Wait! Civilian in play.
重复  有平民
I repeat, civilian in play.
-可以开枪  -请确认
- Clear. - Confirm.
已确认  可以开枪  可以开枪
Confirmed. Clear. Go to green.
见鬼
Shit.
还是运去老地方吗
Are we shipping to the same place?
没错
Yes, sir.
好的
All right.
这是你最棒的一击
That was your best ever.
我简直崇拜
I was impressed.
我打中了哪里
Where'd I hit him?
脖子
Neck.
还是在运行的火车上
On a moving train.
你拍了视频
You took a video?
是啊  我拍了  大家都拍了  你看
Yeah, I took video. Me and everybody else. Look.
-删了  -亨利
- Delete it. - Henry.
拜托
Come on, listen.
找上你之前
Four shooters whiffed on this guy
已经有四个杀手失败了
before you got the call, all right?
四个高手
Four. All of 'em studs.
你一出手就成了
And you ring him up!
干得太漂亮了  我都被感动了  眼睛都湿了
It was beautiful, all right? I got emotional. A tear fell.
删了
Delete it.
我会删的  我会删的
I'll delete it. I'll delete it. All right.
乔治亚州  巴特米尔克海湾
警报
外围被突破
不行
Can't do this.
怎么了  伙计
What's happening, brother?
你还好吗
You all right?
我打中了他的脖子  我瞄准的是脑袋
I got him in his neck. But I was aiming at his head.
其他工作可以掉链子  这工作不行
Other lines of work, you can lose a step. Not this one.
但你还是我们中最厉害的  这行里最厉害的
You're still the best we got. Best anyone's got.
相信我  我懂行
Believe me, I keep track.
今天不喝汽水
Not a soda. Not today.
-什么意思  -给我啤酒
- Meaning? - Give me a beer.
确定吗
Are you sure?
-你真要退休吗  -是的
- Are you really retiring? - Yes, sir.
那我确定
Then I'm sure.
好吧
Okay.
好枪手多得是  德尔
A lot of guys can shoot, Del.
但没你好
They aren't you.
也没有你的经验
They don't have the history you do.
嗯  太多经验就是问题所在
Yeah, I think the history might be the problem.
亨利
Henry.
我们一起经历了那么多  你我二人
We've been through a lot together, you and me.
让世界变得更安全
Made the world safer.
我没法像信任你那样信任新人
I'm just not gonna trust a new guy like I trust you.
当时有个孩子
There was a kid, um...
一个漂亮的小女孩
beautiful little girl,
就在他旁边
right next to him.
偏上十五厘米
If I'm six inches off...
她就死了
she's dead.
你懂吗
Understand?
这次
This time...
是我走运
I got lucky.
那一枪我完全没感觉
I didn't feel the shot.
我本该把握感觉的
Not like I should have.
72次刺杀  德尔
Seventy-two kills, Del.
这些破事最终会影响到你的
That shit starts to mess with you a little bit.
内心深处  就像...
Deep down, it's like...
我的灵魂受了伤
my soul was hurt.
我只想要一丝平静
I just want some peace.
那我该怎么办
So what do I do now?
祝我好运
Wish me well.
早上好
Good morning.
杰里呢
Where's Jerry?
他退休了
Jerry retired.
受不了这种高强度的工作了
Couldn't take any more of this bustling pace.
我是丹妮
I'm Danny.
你好吗  我是亨利
How you doing? Uh, Henry.
我该付23.46美元
I owe you, uh, $23.46.
好的  谢谢  亨利
All right. Thank you, Henry.
你来钓什么
So what are you fishing for?
平和安宁
Peace and quiet.
还有鲭鱼
And mackerel.
要去布里歇尔角吗
Heading out to Breecher's Point?
你建议去那儿吗
Is that what you recommend?
天气这么好  去那里正合适
Well, seems like a nice enough day for it.
看来你不太支持"和平共存"
Not much of a "live and let live" guy, I take it.
我对蜜蜂严重过敏
I'm deathly allergic to bees.
你是学生还是钓鱼专家
You a student or just a fish whisperer?
我在读研究生
Working my way through grad school.
海洋生物学
Marine biology.
乔治亚大学达利恩校区
UGA, Darien?
斗牛犬队是乔治亚大学的橄榄球校队
猛犬加油
Go Dawgs.
在这附近要小心
Well, you be careful around here.
这里的码头  有很多野狗
There's some, uh, dogs out on these docks too.
我能搞定
Nothing I can't handle.
看来我不用问你最近生意怎么样了
Well, I guess I don't have to ask how business is.
你本来也能拥有
Could've been yours.
我也就邀请了你十来次
I only asked you ten times.
兄弟
Hey, brother.
-很高兴见到你  亨利  -我也是  杰克
- It's good to see you, Henry. - You too, Jack.
你这是什么打扮  装性感吗
What are you doing there? Feeling sexy?
谢谢你这么快赶来
Thanks for coming so quickly.
小意思  婚姻生活怎么样
Of course. You still married?
挺好  老婆去巴黎购物了
Yep. Wife's on a shopping trip to Paris.
儿子在寄宿学校
Son's in boarding school.
-你呢  -没有
- You? - Nope.
没老婆没孩子也没巴黎购物游
No wife, no kids, no Paris.
敬下一场战争
Here's to the next war,
-永远不会发生  -永远不会发生
- which is no war. - Which is no war.
有什么事要说
So what you got?
认识他吗
Recognize him?
谁在问
Who's asking?
一个担心你惹了麻烦的老朋友
Your old friend who's afraid you're in trouble.
认识吗
Do you?
我在列日干掉了他
I AMF'ed him in Liège.
他们告诉你他是谁了吗
They tell you who he was?
瓦勒拉·多尔莫夫  恐怖分子
Valery Dormov, terrorist.
不
No.
瓦勒拉·多尔莫夫  分子生物学家
Valery Dormov, molecular biologist,
他在美国工作了三十年
who worked here, in the States, for 30 years.
我看了他的档案
I read his file.
生物恐怖分子
Bioterrorist.
档案被篡改了
The file was spiked.
不知道是谁干的
I don't know by who.
-为什么  -也不知道
- Why? - I don't know that either.
消息来源是谁
Where are you getting this from?
一个朋友
A friend...
另一边的朋友
from the other side.
好吧  我要和他谈谈
All right, well, I need to talk to him.
好啊
Oh, sure.
电话还是视频
Skype? FaceTime?
我要和他谈  杰克
I need to talk to him, Jack.
管他呢
What the hell.
加密笔记
尤里·科瓦奇
布达佩斯
他欠我的
He owes me.
但愿是我错了
I hope I'm wrong.
我只是希望你提高警惕
I just want you to be careful.
这是为了弥补我在国情局工作时错过的生活
It's to make up for all the things I didn't do in my DIA years.
你在国情局这些事干得还少吗
You think you didn't do that in your DIA years?
你这人
This guy.
他们告诉你他是谁了吗
They tell you who he was?
弗吉尼亚州  国防情报局
瓦勒拉·多尔莫夫  恐怖分子
Valery Dormov, terrorist.
不  瓦勒拉·多尔莫夫  分子生物学家
No. Valery Dormov, molecular biologist,
他在美国工作了三十年
who worked here, in the States, for 30 years.
你联系我冒了很大风险
You took a real risk contacting me.
真希望你没这么做
I wish you hadn't.
我还能怎么办
What was I supposed to do?
我爱你  兄弟
I love you, brother.
我也是
You too.
真遗憾
It's a pity.
我一直很欣赏亨利
I always liked Henry.
亨利是国情局的  克雷  他是我的人
Henry is DIA, Clay. He's one of mine.
他知道你骗了他
He knows you lied to him.
我们派了人盯着他
We have a tail on him.
退休的标准流程
Standard protocol for retirement.
行动署副署长
我们会控制住他
He'll be contained.
控制  你说控制亨利·布罗根
Contained? Henry Brogan?
他知道多尔莫夫的线人了
He has Dormov's contact.
他会追踪这条线索
He's gonna pull on that thread
直到提枪找上我们
until he's pointing a gun at our faces.
他的上线呢  秃头那个
What about his handler, the bald guy?
帕特森  他肯定不乐意  但不会违抗我
Patterson? He won't be happy, but he won't cross me.
他会乖乖听话
He'll fall in line.
我会解决这件事
I'll tie this off.
伪装成俄国暗杀
Make it look like a Russian op.
你什么也不许做
You'll do nothing.
我会告诉我的人亨利叛变了
I'll tell my team that Henry's gone rogue.
我能处理
I can handle this.
你四次刺杀多尔莫夫失败  还好意思说
What, after you whiffed four times on Dormov?
不  你需要双子
No. You need Gemini.
我不会让你在美国领土搞刺杀
I will not let you do hits on American soil.
你没有能干掉亨利·布罗根的人
You don't have anyone who can take out Henry Brogan.
我有
I do.
我们自己清理门户  谢谢
We'll clean up our own messes. Thank you.
我们为之努力的一切都岌岌可危
Everything that we've worked for is at stake,
都是拜你的失败所赐
thanks to your failures.
你只有一次机会  可别搞砸了
You have one chance not to screw this up.
拜托你
Please...
给我个惊喜
surprise me.
有收获吗
Any luck?
好吧
Okay.
大多数人会送花
Most guys try flowers
或者放些感觉我会喜欢的浪漫歌曲
or a playlist they think I'll find romantic.
你是国情局的吗
Are you DIA?
你先说说国情局是什么
That depends. What's DIA?
美国舞蹈教练协会[缩写相同]Dance Instructors of America.
是帕特森派你来监视我的吗
Did Patterson send you to surveil me?
-帕特森  -德尔·帕特森
- Patterson. - Del Patterson?
真是巧了  他刚来过这里
Funny coincidence, he was just here.
你暴露了  你的伪装失败了
Look, you're burned. Your cover's blown.
好吧  我刚在听一首马文·盖伊的歌
Okay, well, I was just in the middle of a Marvin Gaye song,
我要继续了
so I'm gonna go back to that.
说出达利恩校区的三栋建筑
Name three buildings on the Darien campus.
-来真的吗  -来吧  海洋生物学家
- Really? - Come on, marine biologist.
罗兹礼堂  麦克沃尔特音乐厅  鲁克大厅
Rhodes Hall, McWhorter Hall, Rooker Hall.
现在我确定你是国情局的了
Now I know you're DIA.
平民会直接让我滚蛋
Civilian would've told me to piss off.
有礼貌的平民就不会
Not a polite civilian.
你不错  很在行
You're good. You're good.
你住哪
Where do you live?
什么
What?
我想看看你家
I want to see your place.
什么
Excuse me?
我相信在你家里找不到任何海洋生物的书
Where I'm sure I won't find a single book on marine biology,
但我肯定能找到一大摞亨利·布罗根的档案
but I'm certain I'll find a big old folder on Henry Brogan.
打扰一下
Excuse me?
好吧  跟你聊天很愉快  但我得去工作了
Okay, this has been fun, but I kind of have to do my job.
抱歉  先生
Sorry, sir. Um--
我有一艘九米多长的快艇
Yeah, I got the 30-foot bowrider.
-好的  -得加点油
- Okay. - Need some gas and--
先生  稍等
Sir. One second.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我能请你喝一杯吗
Can I buy you a drink?
为什么  好让你继续审问我吗
Why, so you can keep interrogating me?
不  我可能会一直道歉
No, I'm probably gonna spend the whole time apologizing.
鹈鹕角如何  周六晚他们有支很棒的乐队
Pelican Point? Sunday nights they have a great band.
拜托了  你什么时候下班
Please. What time do you get off work?
-七点  -我还需要个12伏的舱底泵
- Seven. - I'm gonna also need a 12-volt bilge pump.
-12伏  -好的  七点见
- Twelve-volt... - All right, I'll see you at 7:00.
把你神经病的那面留在家里  拜托了
Just leave the crazy at home, please.
好的
All right.
之前的事不好意思  是我的坏习惯
Sorry about earlier. Bad habits.
我没法轻易相信别人
I don't trust people easily.
但我相信你也一样
But I'm sure you don't either.
为什么这么说
Why would you say that?
国防情报局
丹妮尔·扎卡雷斯基
你从哪弄到的
Where did you get that?
25年的效忠
Twenty-five years of faithful service,
总会交到些朋友
you make some friends.
现在我是真穿帮了
Well, now I'm burned.
彻底糊了
Toast.
帕特森是你的上线吗
Is Patterson running you?
请慢用
All right, here y'all go.
-谢谢  -不客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
加啤威士忌是警察常喝的  你家里有人是警察吗
Boilermaker's a cop drink. You got cops in your family?
我爸生前是联调局的
My dad was FBI.
非常热衷于报效祖国
And, uh, pretty big on serving your country.
"生前"
"Was"?
他想阻止一次银行抢劫  因公殉职了
Yeah, he died off duty, trying to stop a bank robbery.
很遗憾
Sorry about that.
资料说你当过四年海军  巴林第十五舰队的
File says you were four years navy, Fifth Fleet, Bahrain.
是的  我确实很喜欢那片海
Yeah, I did love the sea.
但不喜欢跟几百个士兵一起
Didn't love being stuck in a tin can
困在一个锡罐里
with a couple hundred sailors though.
总比摩加迪休的掩体强
Hey, beats a bunker in Mogadishu.
然后你去了国情局
So, then DIA,
国防秘密服务部
Defense Clandestine Services,
招募和管理特工
recruiting, running assets.
完全没有污点
Not a single demerit.
拜托...
I mean...
然后监察长把你派到了一个码头上
So then the inspector general sticks you on a dock
盯梢一个只是想退休的人
to watch a guy who just wants to retire?
你不会困扰吗
That doesn't bother you?
鹈鹕角
酒吧和妹子
该道别了  亨利
Well, this is adios, Henry.
很高兴能监视你
It's been nice surveilling you.
明天我可能会被派去别的地方
I'll probably be sent somewhere else tomorrow.
要捎你回家吗
Well, you want a ride home?
不用  谢了  我的公寓就在那边
No, thanks, my apartment's just right over there.
亨利  你为什么要退休
Henry, why are you retiring?
我最近发现自己不敢照镜子
I'm finding myself avoiding mirrors lately, so...
我觉得那是个征兆
I'm gonna take that as a sign.
你自己小心
You watch your six out there.
你也是
You too.
晚安  糊妹
Night, Toast.
来看看星星  杰克
You should come look at the stars, Jack.
-你得多练习踢腿  -查理
- We have to work on your kick. - Charlie!
-专心点  亨利  -别这样
- Concentrate, Henry. - Come on!
你都五岁了  这并不难
You're five now, and this isn't hard.
再来
Now, try again.
警报
外围被突破
你好  我是杰克  我在航海
Hi, this is Jack. I'm sailing.
拜托告诉我这意味着我们重出江湖了
Please tell me this means we're back in business.
你在哪
Where are you?
-在做该死的监控任务  -快离开那里
- Just some goddamn surveillance. - Get out of there, now.
别回家  别去你女友家
Do not go home. Do not go to your girl's house.
去车站  用现金买张车票
Go to the bus station. Get a ticket in cash.
-该死  -别用提款机
- Shit. - Do not use an ATM.
去一个没人认识你的地方
Go somewhere where nobody knows you.
你确定吗
You sure?
他们就在我的窗户外
They're outside my window.
抱歉  伙计  我让你也成了目标
I'm sorry, man. I made you a loose end.
别这样  我不会有事的  我怎么跟你联系
Come on, man. I'll be fine. How do I get in contact with you?
不联系  谁也别联系
You don't. Don't contact anybody.
尤其是国情局的人
Especially anybody from the DIA.
现在就把你的手机扔了
And get rid of your phone now.
不行  别这样  亨利  别...
Nah, come on, Henry, man. Stop--
马里诺
Marino?
现在不是用枪的时候
It's not gun time.
现在是喝咖啡的时候
It's coffee time.
你有机密文件销毁袋吗
Do you have a burn bag?
先告诉我你来这里做什么
First tell me what you're doing here.
有人刚派了一队人来杀我
Somebody just sent a team to kill me.
而你还在睡觉
And you're still asleep.
说明你并不知情  对吧
So that means you didn't know about it, correct?
我当然不知道  不然我肯定会告诉你
No, of course not. I would've told you.
说明下一个就是你了
That means you're next.
穿好衣服
Get dressed.
那些船都有备用钥匙在办公室吧
All the boats have dupe keys in the office, right?
有快艇吗
Got a fast one?
感受到大海的召唤了吗
Feeling the call of the sea?
他在哪
Where is he?
你可以现在告诉我
You can tell me now--
放下...
Drop--
贱人
Bitch!
你可以现在告诉我
You can tell me now,
或者等五分钟后你少了几颗牙再说
or you can tell me in five minutes minus your teeth.
反正你总会告诉我的
But you're gonna tell me.
我数到有三声  你带了几个人
I counted three. How many did you bring?
谁派你来的
Who sent you?
你可以现在告诉我  或者等五分钟后
You can tell me now, or you can tell me in five minutes
你少了几颗牙再说
minus your teeth.
你没事吧
You good?
-是拉西特  -你怎么知道
- It's Lassiter. - How do you know?
如果你上了这艘船  你就要抛弃
If you get on this boat, you're leaving behind
你认识的一切人和事
everything and everybody you've ever known.
你明白吗
Do you understand that?
害怕是好事
Scared is good.
说明你很警觉
It means you're alert.
我还从来没被追杀过呢
Never had anybody try to kill me before.
重点是他没杀成
Yeah, well, the important thing is he didn't.
你怕什么  除了蜜蜂
What scares you? Other than bees.
溺水
Drowning.
你就是这么收拾自己的烂摊子的
So this is you cleaning up your own messes.
别跟我说教了
Spare me the lecture.
这就像看着兴登堡号撞到了泰坦尼克号上
It's like watching the Hindenburg crash into the Titanic.
我们要怎么处理亨利
Tell me what we're going to do about Henry.
亨利·布罗根和其他士兵一样
Henry Brogan is like any other soldier.
当他们年轻而愚昧时
When they're young and stupid,
你说什么他们都信
they believe anything you tell them.
然后他们会变老  会老化
Then they get older. They wear out.
会渐渐生出良知
Grow a conscience.
所以我们需要新品种的士兵
This is why we need a new breed of soldier.
双子会处理的
Gemini will handle this.
抱歉  我不能允许
I'm sorry, I can't allow that.
我不是在征求你的同意
I'm not asking your permission.
你想去找你的上司们吗
You want to go to your bosses?
他们肯定很想听听我们的叛变项目
I'm sure they'd love to hear about our little rogue project.
我会做得像俄国人干的
I'll make it look like a Russian hit.
你给亨利安排国葬
You give Henry a state funeral.
棺材上覆盖国旗  鸣枪21响
Flag on the coffin, 21-gun salute.
你念个感人的致辞  大家都会哭
You give a nice speech. Everyone cries.
他会作为英雄被铭记
He'll be remembered as a hero.
生活会继续下去
Life goes on.
-亨利的生活不会了  -得了吧
- Not for Henry. - Oh, come on.
亨利这样的杂碎生来就是当炮灰的
Mutts like Henry were born to be collateral damage.
咱们就别假装不是这样了
Let's not pretend otherwise.
你有特工就位了吗
Do you have an asset in place?
我有最完美的人选
I have the perfect asset.
-好了  -就...
- All right. - Just--
好了  我没事
All right, I'm good.
你饿吗
You hungry?
饿死了  但那些东西三年前就过期了
Yeah, I'm starving, but those things expired three years ago.
是吗
Really?
还是挺好吃的
Still taste good.
那人还有牙的时候  他说你叛变了
While he still had teeth, that guy said you were the rogue.
你信了他
And you believed him?
99%确信他是在说谎
99% sure he was lying.
剩的那1%很折磨人  对吧
That 1% sucks, doesn't it?
亨利  这种事在你身上发生过吗
Henry, has this ever happened to you before?
哪部分
Which part?
你自己的政府想杀你
Your own government trying to kill you.
没有  这是新鲜事
Nah, that's new.
你在局里也有一阵子了
You've been Agency a while.
你能猜到是为了什么吗
Can't you guess what this is all about?
相信我  如果我能猜到
Trust me, if I could,
我现在就不会跟你一起度这个假了
I would not be on this lovely vacation with you.
好吧
Well...
等我当上局里的老大
when I'm head of the Agency,
我们可不会这么对待退休员工
we're gonna handle retirement very differently.
好兄弟
My man.
巴伦·图尔斯来接布罗根  两位乘客
Baron Tours here to pick up Brogan, party of two!
-很高兴见到你  伙计  -我也是
- Good to see you, man. - You too.
丹妮  这是巴伦
Danny, meet the Baron.
中年堕落人士  也是我认识的最棒的飞行员
Middle-aged reprobate and best pilot I've ever known.
丹妮  巴伦
Danny, Baron.
你好  糊妹
Hey, Toast.
按你的要求给你们弄了一次性电话
Got you burners, as requested.
目前你们可以躲在我在卡塔赫纳的家里
For now, you can hole up in my place in Cartagena.
没人认识你们  很安全
You'd be anonymous and safe.
现在情况有点糟  伙计
Yeah, we're kinda in the shit here, man.
我觉得杰克死了
I think Jack is dead.
-天啊  -是啊
- Jesus. - Yeah.
-有人跟踪你吗  -没有
- Anyone follow you? - Nah.
早晚的事  我们走
They will. Let's go.
我能吃点饼干吗
Can I have one of those crackers?
-当然  -谢了
- Sure. - Thanks.
他在家也这样吗
Does he do this at home?
应该不会吧  我不知道
I don't think so. I don't know.
-你会吗  -不会
- Do you? - No.
如果你知道在家做这种事不合适
If it's inappropriate to do this sort of thing at home...
你为什么认为在科学课上做
why would you think it's appropriate to do it
就合适呢
in your science class?
说不好  可能是因为科学特别无聊吧
I don't know. Probably because science is so wicked boring.
喂
Hello.
我猜你是真不想让我退休
Guess you really didn't want me to retire.
亨利  你没事  太好了
Henry, you're okay! Thank God!
少来
Stop it.
马里诺死了吗
Is Marino dead?
是的
Yes.
杰克·威利斯呢
Jack Willis?
不是我干的  都不是我干的  亨利  我发誓
It wasn't me. None of this was me, Henry. I swear it.
我信任过你  德尔
I trusted you, Del.
你仍然可以信任我  我换个号码打给你
You still can. Let me call you on another line.
604-555-0131.
你有三十秒时间
You got 30 seconds.
不好意思
Hey, excuse me.
要是我给你一百块
Could I borrow your phone
能把你的手机
for five minutes if I give you,
借我用五分钟吗
like, a hundred bucks?
我们先说说是谁下令
We'll start with whose idea it was
派了一队人去扎卡雷斯基的公寓
to send a team to Agent Zakarewski's apartment.
有那个必要吗
Was that necessary?
那也不是我的决定
Also not my call.
她是检察长的手下  不是我的手下
She's working for the inspector general, not me.
-她和你在一起吗  -对  但不是自愿的
- Is she with you? - Yes. Not voluntarily.
好  听着  我不想在电话里说这个
Okay, listen. This is not something I want to say over the phone.
我在我孩子的学校里
I'm at my kid's goddamn school.
这都是怎么回事
What the hell is all of this?
我们有个麻烦
We have a problem.
双子
Gemini.
你的老友在和简妮特·拉西特一伙人合作
Your old friend, working with Janet Lassiter and her people.
我没法阻止他们
I can't stop them.
好吧  多尔莫夫
Okay. Dormov.
他和双子有关吗
Did he have something to do with Gemini?
多尔莫夫  你说他是俄国恐怖分子
Dormov, the guy that you had me pop on the train
让我在他坐火车时把他干掉了
because you said he was a Russian terrorist.
他曾为双子效力吗
Was he working for Gemini?
曾经是
Once upon a time.
所以你让我替克雷·威利斯杀人
So you got me pulling triggers for Clay Verris.
亨利  我也后悔不够坦诚  但是...
Henry, I regret my lack of candor, but listen--
你还骗过我多少次  德尔
How many other times you do this to me, Del?
你篡改过多少次档案
How many times you spike a file,
送我去杀那些罪不至死的人
send me off to AMF somebody who didn't deserve it?
从没有过  只有这一次
Never ever. This was a one-off.
我用我儿子的命发誓
I swear on my son's life.
好吧  扎克雷斯基探员与此事无关
All right, look, Agent Zakarewski is not a part of this.
亨利  我们能解决的  我发誓
Henry, we can fix this, I swear.
但我需要你们俩都回来
But I need both of you to come back.
回去什么下场  德尔
To what, Del?
好  双子
Okay. Gemini.
你对它知道多少
What do you know about it?
克雷·威利斯的私人准军事组织
Privatized paramilitary owned by Clay Verris.
局里经常与他们合作  还有别的吗
Agency does a lot of business with them. Is there more?
巴伦和我在海军时是威利斯的手下
Baron and I served under Verris in the marines.
巴拿马  科威特  索马利亚
Panama, Kuwait, Somalia.
他退役之后
After he left the military,
成立了双子
he started Gemini
想雇佣我们
and tried to hire us.
我们都拒绝了
We both told him no.
不过我够聪明  搬到了2400公里之外
Except I was smart enough to move 1,500 miles away.
是啊
Yeah.
我搞砸了
I blew that one.
哥伦比亚  卡塔赫纳
威利斯不择手段除掉目标
Verris gets billions of dollars a year
以此每年获利数十亿美金
to take out targets any way he sees fit.
双子就是做这个的
That's Gemini.
暗中绑架  折磨
Off-book kidnappings, tortures.
要是你需要
They're who you call
十二名沙特王子
when you need 12 Saudi princes
无声无息地消失
to quietly disappear
或是想找人训练你的敢死队  联系他们就行
or you want somebody to train your death squads.
学了六周的狙击后
Six weeks into sniper school,
克雷·威利斯带我上船开出海八公里
Clay Verris takes me out on this boat about five miles.
在我脚上捆了重物  把我推下船
Ties these weights to my ankles, tosses me overboard,
让我能踩水多久就踩多久
tells me tread water as long as I can.
他不知道你害怕...
And he didn't know about your fear of--
他当然知道  就是因为这个
Of course he did. That was the point.
那你做了什么
So what did you do?
我踩水  踩到踩不动
I tread water for as long as I could.
然后我溺水了
And then I drowned.
死了
Dead.
他把我捞上去  按压我的胸膛
He fished me out, paddled my chest.
告诉我  我准备好为他效力了
Told me I was now ready to serve under his command.
来一杯
A toast.
敬下一次战争
To the next war,
-永远不会发生  -永远不会发生
- which is no war. - Which is no war.
永远不会发生
No war.
我们早上再想办法
We'll figure it out in the morning.
现在我们都需要休息一下
Right now we could use some shut-eye.
没问题  你们要一间房还是...
Sure. Uh, you folks want one room or--
两间
Two.
两间  两间
Two. Two.
行  你愿意的话我可以让他睡车库
Well, yeah. I can put him in the garage if you want.
行  两间就可以
All right, two rooms will be fine.
就是让你们选一下  行  这边走
Just giving you options. Okay, right this way.
狙击手  屋顶  我离开  他会跟上来
Sniper. Rooftop. I leave, he's gonna follow.
我要你和巴伦去安全的地方  好吗
I need you to go with Baron someplace safe. All right?
枪手  在屋顶上
Shooter. On the roof.
你真是个要命的客人  知道吗
You're a shitty houseguest, you know that?
他们怎么找到我们的
How the hell did they find us?
她是好人  真的是好人
She's good. She's really good.
她只是不了解内幕
She just doesn't know what she doesn't know.
照顾好她  行吗
Take care of her, all right?
行
All right.
站住
Stop right there!
你是谁
Who are you?
我不想朝你开枪
I don't want to shoot you!
行
Fine.
别朝我开枪
Don't shoot me.
介意我朝你开枪吗
Mind if I shoot you?
刚刚在屋顶上我本可以杀了你
I could've killed you on the roof!
也许你是该杀了我
Maybe you should have.
他们给你看我的照片了吗
Did they show you a picture of me?
嗯  你看着好老
Yeah. You look old.
小子  你再走近一步
Kid, you take one step closer,
我就别无选择了
you're gonna leave me no choice.
放开  放开
Stop! Stop! Stop!
让开  让开
Move! Move!
别挡路
Get out of the way!
Out of the way!
停  停  停
Stop! Stop! Stop!
那到底是谁
Who the hell was that?
国家警察
布罗根
Brogan.
谢谢  先生
Thank you, sir.
-谢谢  队长  -不客气
- Thank you, Captain. - No problem.
你家已经暴露了  给我找个视野开阔的地方
Your place is burned. Get me somewhere I can see him coming.
我想持枪闯进去
I wanted to go in there guns blazing,
但她觉得用外交手段更合理
but she thought the diplomatic approach made more sense.
是啊  开枪可能更亲切点
Yeah, gunfire might've been kinder.
做得不错
Great work in there.
现在怎么办
What now?
我要你送我去布达佩斯
I need you to get me to Budapest.
-布达佩斯有什么  -布达佩斯有什么
- What's in Budapest? - What's in Budapest?
杰克的线人  尤里
Jack's informant, Yuri.
他们追杀我不是因为我要退休
These guys aren't trying to kill me because I want to retire.
他们追杀我
They're coming after me
是因为他们认为
because they think Jack
杰克告诉了我机密信息
told me something classified.
尤里应该知道这事
Yuri ought to know about it.
抱歉  搭档  我的阿兹特克飞不了那么远
I'm sorry, partner, my Aztec doesn't have that kind of range.
我希望能借一架飞得了的
Well, I was hoping we would borrow something that does.
比如湾流飞机
Maybe a G?
借人家的湾流飞机
Taking someone's Gulfstream?
得是真爱才能借得出吧
I mean, you'd really have to love a guy to do that.
我刚好认识这么一个人  等我一下
I know just the fella. Give me a minute.
亨利
Henry?
你有孩子吗
Did you ever have a kid?
没有  怎么
No. Why?
骑摩托那个人
Guy on the motorcycle.
你注意到他有什么奇怪的地方了吗
Did you notice anything funny about him?
我注意到他非常厉害
I noticed he was very good.
对
Right.
他的脸呢
And the face?
相似之处
Similarity?
我也注意到那点了
Yeah, I noticed that too.
那
So...
你从未有过长期情人吗
You never had a long-term relationship?
没  除非把你算上
No. Not unless we count you.
有没有可能你有个孩子但不知道
Is it possible that you could've had a kid without knowing it?
不可能
No.
-那你怎么解释...  -丹妮
- Then how do you explain-- - Danny.
别说了
All right?
顺便  谢谢你
Thank you, by the way.
谢什么
For?
你离开巴伦的公寓  好让他不瞄上我
For leaving Baron's apartment so I wouldn't be a target.
在乔治亚时
Coming to get me in Georgia
你可以自己逃命  但却来接我
when you could've just run for your life.
我只是想把你送上一架私人飞机
I just wanted to put you on a private plane
免费送去你去匈牙利
and give you a free trip to Hungary.
我在那能找到...
Where I'm gonna find...
匈牙利人
Hungarians.
对
Right.
我看到他时...
When I saw him...
仿佛看到了一个鬼魂
it was like I was seeing a ghost.
一个持枪的鬼魂
A ghost with a gun.
就像我抢下的每一个鬼魂
Like... every trigger I've ever pulled.
乔治亚州  格伦维尔市
我让你留在哥伦比亚待命
I told you to stay in Colombia and await orders.
我想和你谈谈
I wanted to talk to you.
他非常厉害
He's very good.
他是最厉害的
He's the best.
所以我才派了你
That's why I sent you.
他提前预判了我的每一个动作
He knew every move of mine before I made it.
我本来能抓住他  我能开枪
I'd have him, right there, and I'd take the shot...
然后他就会死
and he'd be gone.
就像一个鬼魂
Like a ghost.
你看到他的脸了吗
Did you get a look at his face?
没看清
Not really.
他站在楼梯上面  我在脏镜子里看到了
I saw him up the stairs, through a dirty mirror.
我以为你在屋顶上
I thought you were on the roof.
我本来在  他知道我在那里  我必须跳下来
I was. He got a line on me. I had to jump down.
我们都是怎么训练的
What do we always drill?
你要占据高地
You hold the high ground.
把他逼到墙边  别让他逃掉
You put his back against the wall, and you don't let him go.
我知道
I know that.
整件事都很奇怪
The whole thing was weird.
很...反常
It was... wiggy.
怎么说
How?
说不清  就像我是在旁观一样
I don't know, it was as if I were watching it all.
他是谁
Who is he?
小克  你这种纠结
Junior, this thing that you're struggling with,
这种陌生感  这是恐惧
this strangeness, it's fear.
不要厌恶它
Don't hate it.
要依靠它
Lean into it.
接受它  然后战胜它
Embrace it and then overcome it.
你只需要跨过这道坎  儿子
You are right on the threshold, son.
只差一步了
This close.
你饿吗
You hungry?
是的
Yes, sir.
来碗麦片怎么样
Bowl of cereal sound good?
好的
Yes, sir.
上
Go!
手榴弹
Grenade!
演习完成
谢谢  可以了  回来吧
Thank you! That's it! Back up!
快点  大家回到原地
Hurry up! Everybody back to one.
大家回到原地
Everybody back to one.
回到原地  快
Back to one! Let's go!
-很多新人  -是的
- Lots of new faces. - Yep.
双子
他们会是第一批踏上也门的人
They'll be the first boots on the ground in Yemen.
他们理解交火的原则吗
Do they understand the rules of engagement,
还是只要看到动的东西就开枪
or just, whatever moves, they shoot it?
他们是精英  训练有素
They're elite. They're disciplined.
如果能从公寓窗口将目标
And if they get a clean shot at their target
一击致命  他们会毫不犹豫
through an apartment window, they'll take it.
你应该在去布达佩斯的路上反思一下
You should think about that on your way to Budapest.
亨利刚到那里
Henry's just landed there.
你要出发了
You're moving out.
匈牙利  布达佩斯
安妮可
Aniko?
感谢你抽出时间
Thank you for your time.
样本在这里
Here are the samples.
两天后给你结果
This I can do for you in two days.
两小时后就要
This I need in two hours.
我们要和尤里见面
We got a meeting with Yuri.
他答应和我们谈谈
He agreed to sit with us.
你还好吗
You all right?
我知道他为什么和你一样厉害了  亨利
I think I know why he's as good as you, Henry.
他就是你
He is you.
什么
What?
这儿有个DNA实验室  我给了他们样本
There's a DNA lab here. I gave them samples.
你的和他戴的那个棒球帽上面的
Yours and the baseball cap he was wearing.
他  他和你那么像
He just-- He looked so much like you,
我以为他一定是你儿子  所以我...
I thought he had to be your son, so I...
他们做了三次检测
They did three tests.
你和他的DNA
Your DNA and his.
三次结果都完全相同
All three came back identical.
不是相似  是完全相同
Not close. Identical.
"同一个人"的相同
As in "the same person."
他是你的克隆体
He's your clone.
他们以为我弄错了
They thought I'd made a mistake,
给的两个样本都是同一个人
given them samples of the same person,
但我没有
but I didn't.
他就是你
He is you.
怎么可能
How's that even possible?
很复杂  但可以做到
It's complicated, but it's doable.
只需要一位代孕母亲和一份DNA样本
All you'd really need is a surrogate mother and a DNA sample.
如果他们可以克隆人
If they could clone a person,
他们应该克隆更多的医生或科学家
you'd think they'd clone more doctors or scientists,
而不是我
not me.
他们可以克隆纳尔逊·曼德拉
They could've cloned Nelson Mandela.
纳尔逊·曼德拉无法在两公里之外
Nelson Mandela couldn't kill a man on a moving train
杀死行驶中的火车上的人
from two kilometers away.
尤里
Yuri.
布罗根先生
Mr. Brogan.
首先我必须坦白
Before we begin, I must confess,
我久仰你的大名了
I have admired your work for many years.
等等  你知道我是谁
Wait. So you know who I am?
老听众  首次拨打热线
A longtime listener, first-time caller,
贵国是这么说的吧
as they say in your country.
我想祝贺你的退休
I would congratulate you on your retirement,
但你的最后一次任务没有彻底完成吧
but your last job has loose ends, yes?
是  我的政府骗了我  然后想杀我
Yeah, well, my government lied to me then tried to kill me,
你是说这个吧
if that's what you mean.
是的
Yes.
在俄罗斯  这就是我们的日常
In Russia, we call that "Tuesday."
但在美国  你们就伤心了
But Americans, it hurts your feelings.
说吧
So...
多尔莫夫为什么想回俄罗斯
So why was Dormov trying to go back to Russia
为什么要派我去杀他
and why was I sent to kill him?
好  马上说正事  正宗美国人
Yes, down to business. Ooh. Very American.
你是个忙人啊
You are a busy man.
我们都是杰克的朋友
We were both friends with Jack.
他是个好人
He was a good man.
我和你一样都为他的死而哀悼
I'm mourning his death, like you.
但你来这里  而我还没杀了你的原因
But the reason you are here and I have not killed you...
暂时还没杀
yet...
就是我们有共同的敌人
is we share a common enemy.
克雷·威利斯
Clay Verris.
他把多尔莫夫骗到西方  资助他的实验室
He lured Dormov to the West, funded his lab.
现在你也见过了他们孕育的果实
And now you have met the fruits of their labor.
克隆羊多莉诞生于1996年
Dolly the sheep was cloned in '96.
-但在1995年  -我是那只羊
- But in '95-- - I was the sheep.
把这当成是赞美吧
Take it as a compliment.
仅有你一人
And you are the only one.
威利斯把你的克隆体当自己的儿子养大
With your DNA, Verris raised the boy as his own son,
把他训练成完美杀手
trained him to be the perfect assassin.
那多尔莫夫为什么想要离开
So why was Dormov trying to leave?
我们一直都想诱他回来
For years, we tried to lure him back.
都是徒劳
Nothing.
然后在去年  他们闹翻了
Then last year, they had a falling out.
多尔莫夫害怕了  找到了我
Dormov got scared, reached out to me.
那我...
So, I--
你还是没解释为什么我被派去杀他
That still doesn't explain why I was sent to kill him.
我们有迹象表明多尔莫夫取得了重大突破
We have indications Dormov made a breakthrough.
人类DNA改造
Modified human DNA.
可以批量生产的途径
A path to mass production.
多尔莫夫想要士兵更强壮  更聪明
But Dormov wanted soldiers to be stronger, smarter.
但威利斯
Verris...
威利斯想要的是别的
Verris wanted something else.
什么别的
What something else?
布罗根先生
Mr. Brogan,
你是你这行最出色的人
you are the best at what you do.
但你也会疲惫  也有恐惧  怀疑
But still you get tired. You have fears, doubts.
你会感觉痛苦  或许会懊悔
You feel pain, perhaps remorse.
你有良心
You have a conscience.
这让你有人性
This makes you human,
但不是最好的士兵
but suboptimal as a soldier.
不够完美
Less than perfect.
不够赚钱
Less profitable.
克雷顿·威利斯在用DNA扮演上帝的角色
Clayton Verris is playing God with DNA.
必须要阻止他
He must be stopped.
如果有那么危险  为什么不发射导弹
If it's that dangerous, why not send a missile?
炸了他的实验室
Blow up his lab.
我们就是在这么做
That is what we're doing.
只不过现在的导弹是你
Except you are the missile.
祝你好运
I wish you luck.
还有一件事
One last thing.
两天前你从家里逃走的那次
Your escape from home two days ago?
真是厉害
Amazing work.
我全程都替你紧张
I was on the edge of my seat.
等等  什么
Wait. What?
你怎么知道这个
How the hell do you know about that?
我可是你的忠实粉丝啊
I'm a big fan. What can I say?
即使他所说的只有一半是真的
If even half of what he's saying is true,
我们都要和这个孩子谈谈
we gotta talk to this kid.
不然的话你一直都不安全
You're not gonna be safe until you do.
如果你的五十岁本体突然出现告诉你
So you think if your 50-year-old self showed up
你是她的克隆体  能让你冷静下来吗
and told you you were her clone, that would make you calmer?
五十一岁
Fifty-one.
-什么  -随口一说
- What? - Just saying.
你知道你五十一了吧  亨利
You know you're 51, Henry?
-四舍五入  -好吧
- I'm rounding. - Right.
他是你不愿看的镜子  亨利
He's the mirror you don't want to look into, Henry.
但他是我们找到威利斯的最好机会
But he's our best shot at getting to Verris.
简妮特·拉西特
Janet Lassiter?
你是谁
Who wants to know?
我来给你传信  女士
Got a message for you, ma'am,
信息来自一个给我的
from a man who transferred $1,000
羽毛币账户转账一千美元的人
into my Feathercoin account just to make sure you got it.
这人叫什么名字
Does this person have a name?
他叫"给我的羽毛币账户转账一千美元的人"
His name is "$1,000 Into My Feathercoin Account."
"你好  简妮特
"Hello, Janet.
在你打算再次追杀我之前  考虑一下
Before you try to kill me again, consider this:
你家地址是卡罗尔街1362号
Your home address is 1362 Carrol Grove.
安全警报器密码是1776
The security alarm code is 1776.
你每天早晨6点12醒来
You awaken at 6:12 every morning
6点42去买一杯加浓低因豆奶拿铁
and stop for your decaf soy latte with an extra shot by 6:42.
每晚你都站在你家客厅的大窗户前
Every night you stand in front of your huge living room window,
喝一杯金快活玛格丽特
sipping a Jose Cuervo margarita,
电视里放着《法医档案》
with Forensic Files on the TV,
身上穿着舒适的家居服"
wearing your nice, comfy sweatpants."
我是拉西特
This is Lassiter.
你的十点钟和两点钟方向有枪手
There are shooters at your ten and two.
你敢站起来的话  就AMF了
Get up off of that chair, you will be AMF'ed.
如果我觉得这个世界还需要一个我
Now, if I thought the world needed another me,
我会生个孩子
I would've had a kid.
那个项目在我上任之前就存在了
The program predates my arrival at the Agency.
你要知道这一点
You must know that.
是啊  典型官僚回答  出了问题就甩锅
Yeah, perfect DC answer: Something goes wrong, duck!
给骑车小伙小费
Tip the bike guy.
你可以走了
You can go.
我劫持了你的探员
Now, I have your agent with me against her will.
丹妮尔·扎卡雷斯基
Danielle Zakarewski.
她想回去
She wants to come in.
行
Fine.
她像我一样是个爱国者
Like me, she is a patriot.
与我不同的是  她依旧想在接下来的几十年里
Unlike me, she still wants to spend the next couple decades
为你们这些混蛋卖力工作
scoring touchdowns for you assholes.
她的安全无商议余地
Her safety is nonnegotiable.
十点钟和两点钟方向  简妮特
Ten and two, Janet.
简妮特的加浓低因豆奶拿铁
Decaf soy latte with an extra shot for Janet.
我只愿把她交给
The only person I'll turn her over to
你们派去卡塔赫纳追杀我的人
is the guy you sent after me in Cartagena.
别想着派别人来
Don't even think about sending anybody else.
家人团聚  很温情啊
Family reunion. Very sweet.
继续嘴硬
Yeah. Keep it up.
你会成为我第一个免费杀的人
You'll be the first person I ever killed for free.
你能让他多快赶到布达佩斯
How quickly can you get him to Budapest?
五分钟
Five minutes?
好
Good.
她今晚午夜会在沃伊达奇城堡的庭院里
She'll be in the courtyard of the Vajdahunyad Castle at midnight tonight.
享用你的拿铁吧
Enjoy your latte.
AMF是什么意思
What's AMF?
"再见  狗娘养的"
"Adios, motherfucker."
他是怎么知道我们在这里的
How the hell does he know we're here?
会成功的  对吧
This is gonna work, right?
是的
Yes.
你怎么知道
How do you know?
我知道他的喜好
I know his taste.
等等  你是说你对我有兴趣
Wait, are you saying you're attracted to me?
现在的我  当然不会
Me? Now? Hell, no.
但我的年轻纯真版  或许会
But the younger, less-mature version, maybe.
在乔治亚时我去找你
When I came for you in Georgia,
根本不用思考
I didn't have to think about that.
那是本能
It was instinct.
他也有那种本能
He was born with that too.
再说了  他想杀我
Besides, he wants me.
右转
Right.
庭院真漂亮
Lovely courtyard.
抱歉  女士
I'm sorry, ma'am.
继续进行之前  我需要你脱掉衣服
Before we go any farther, I'm gonna need you to strip.
你说什么
Beg your pardon?
需要确定你没带监听器
Need to be certain you're not wearing a wire.
好吧  首先
Okay, first of all,
你叫我"女士"
"Ma'am"?
我受的教育是要尊敬长辈
I was raised to respect my elders.
请脱掉衣服
Take your clothes off, please.
请转身
Turn around, please.
看来你喜欢做事细致
I see you like to be thorough.
谨慎让我能活命
Caution has kept me alive.
打给他的一次性电话
Call his burner.
谢谢
Thank you.
布罗根
Brogan.
十二分钟后  我会对她后脑开两枪
In 12 minutes, I'm putting two bullets in the back of her head.
你受到的命令是安全交接她
Your orders are to deliver her safely.
我受到的命令是杀了你
My orders are to kill you.
你熟悉地下墓穴的石英室吗
Are you familiar with the Quartz Chamber of the catacombs?
不行
Negative.
要在显眼的地方  让我能看到你
We're doing this someplace visible, where I can see you.
现在你只剩十一分钟了
Now you have 11 minutes.
穿上衣服  我们开车去
Get dressed. We're taking a ride.
出租车真是聪明的主意
Cab was a smart move.
你来自哪里
Where are you from?
你的礼节  是南方的
Your formality, it's Southern.
如果你要拿我当诱饵  还可能杀了我
You know, if you're gonna use me as bait and possibly murder me,
那你起码能陪我聊几句
then the least you can do is indulge me in some conversation.
在亚特兰大附近
Just outside Atlanta.
你们两个有很多相似点
You two have a lot in common.
我表示怀疑
I doubt that.
你会很惊讶的
You'd be surprised.
我最开始也是跟踪他
You know, I started following him too.
就像你现在这样
Just like you're doing.
然后我渐渐了解了他
Then I got to know him.
他心胸宽广  像你一样
He's got a big heart, like you.
你怎么了解我的心
What do you know about my heart?
我知道你有心
I know that you have one.
我还知道它在告诉你
And I know that it's telling you
你这次被指派的任务不对劲
that something about the job you've been given isn't right.
任务就是任务  女士
A job is a job, ma'am.
真想知道你付了管理员多少钱
I wonder how much you paid the custodian.
左转
Left.
解开锁链
Undo the chain.
地下室
Basement.
你肯定很了解这个城市
You must really know the city.
我经常看《国家地理》
I watch a lot of Nat Geo.
-上面写着"禁入"  -请
- It says "Off-Limits." - Ma'am.
真想知道有多少人被埋葬在这里
Wonder how many people are buried down here.
站在那里
Stand over there.
走
Go.
如果你把灯都熄灭了
If you knock out all the lights,
出去时怎么看得到自己布置的绊线
how are you gonna see your own trip wire on the way out?
手榴弹可不是闹着玩的  我懂你的想法
A grenade is no joke. I mean, I get the idea.
黑暗让他最强的狙击无法施展
Darkness neutralizes his biggest strength,
近距离对你有利  是吗
and close quarters favors you, right?
他扔手榴弹会把我也杀死
I mean, he can't throw a grenade without killing me too.
但如果他用毒气呢
But what if he tries gas?
或者某种镇静剂
You know? Or some sort of sedative agent?
想我前面去了  防毒面具和夜视镜  聪明
Way ahead of me. Gas mask and night vision. Very smart.
-那边  -还有索带
- Over there. - And zip ties!
肯定是给我准备的
These must be for me.
不过我能问你件事吗
But can I ask you something?
你说个不停真的会给我留出回答的间隙吗
Would you actually stop talking long enough for me to answer?
你对他了解多少
How much do you know about him?
有人告诉你为什么要杀他吗
Anybody tell you why they wanted him dead?
他疯了
Guy cracked.
一夜之内杀了八名特工  还有他的探子
Killed eight ops in a single night and his spotter.
-他们这么告诉你的吗  -他就是这么做的
- That's what they told you? - That's what he did.
不  并不是
No. No, not exactly.
那些特工被杀那晚我也在场
I was there the night all those operatives were hit.
他们是被双子派去杀他还有我的
They'd been sent to kill him, and me, by Gemini.
或许这不算什么
And not that it matters,
但他的探子是在维吉尼亚被害
but his spotter was shot in Virginia,
其余人是在萨凡纳丧命
and the rest of those men went down in Savannah.
亨利确实能远距离射击  但打不了那么远
Henry can shoot long-distance, but he can't shoot that long.
拜托你好好想想  你觉得这说得通吗
Come on. Just think. Does that make any sense to you?
你明白我在说什么吗
Do you understand what I'm saying?
这不...
It doesn't--
好多了
Better.
我操
Fuck you!
起来  走
Get up. Go.
站住别动
Stay right there.
-谢谢  -给
- Thank you. - Here.
你知道怎么点吗
You know how to light one of those?
老天  亨利
Jesus, Henry.
谢谢你提醒我有手榴弹
Thanks for the tip on the grenade.
你一直在和他说话
You were talking to him the whole time.
没错
Yeah.
搜身要么搜彻底  要么不搜
You either search somebody or you don't.
事先声明
And for the record...
我不想杀你
I do not want to kill you.
但若有必要我绝对会动手
But I absolutely will if I have to.
克雷·威利斯怎么跟你说我的
What did Clay Verris tell you about me?
好吧  我跟你讲讲他的事
Okay. Well, let me tell you about him.
因为我和威利斯先生非常熟悉
Because I know Mr. Verris very well.
他怎么开始训练你的
How'd he start you?
猎鸟  猎兔吗
Hunting birds? Rabbit?
大概十二岁让你升级为猎鹿
About 12 years old, moved you up to deer?
我猜十九或二十岁时
I'm guessing 19, 20 years old
他第一次让你对人开枪
the first time he ordered you to shoot a person.
我说得对吗
Any of this ringing true?
没错
Yeah.
他告诉你要"依靠恐惧"
He told you to "lean into your fear,"
因为你是"战士
because you were "a warrior,
拥有保护弱者的伟大天赋"
blessed with great gifts to defend the weak."
但他无法阻止那个声音
But he couldn't stop the noise...
你内心深处某一部分总感觉
that secret part of you that always felt
和其他人有点不一样
a little different than everybody else.
感觉像个怪胎
Part that felt like a weirdo.
你什么也不知道
You don't know shit.
小子  你里里外外我都知道
Kid, I know you inside out and backwards.
你对蜜蜂过敏  讨厌香菜
You're allergic to bees. You hate cilantro.
你总是打四次喷嚏
You always sneeze four times.
谁都讨厌香菜
Everybody hates cilantro.
你小心细致
You're meticulous.
周密  有纪律  坚持不懈
Thorough. Disciplined. Relentless.
你喜欢解谜
You love puzzles.
你下棋  对不对
You're a chess player. Right?
我猜下得还挺好
Good, too, I bet.
但你一直受失眠的折磨
But you suffer from insomnia.
你的大脑从不让你睡
Your mind never lets you sleep.
即使睡了也遭受噩梦困扰
And even when it does, it attacks you with nightmares.
我说的是那种凌晨三点
I'm talking 'bout those three-o'clock-in-the-morning,
"快来人救我"那种噩梦
somebody-please-save-me kind of nightmares.
还有怀疑  那是最糟糕的
And then there's the doubts, and those are the worst.
你讨厌它们  你讨厌自己有怀疑
You hate 'em, and you hate yourself for having 'em.
它们让你感觉软弱
They make you feel weak.
真正的士兵不会怀疑  对吗
A real soldier doesn't doubt, right?
你唯一真正感到开心的时候
The only time you ever truly feel happy
就是趴在地上即将扣下扳机时
is when you're flat on your belly about to squeeze a trigger.
那一刻  世界完全说得通了
And in that moment, the world makes perfect sense.
你觉得我是怎么知道这些的
How do you think I know all of that?
我才不在乎你怎么知道的
I don't give a shit how you know anything.
看着我  蠢蛋
Look at me, dummy!
看看我们
Look at us!
二十五年前
Twenty-five years ago,
你父亲偷了我的血用来克隆
your father took my blood and he cloned me.
他用我克隆出了你
He made you from me.
我们的DNA完全相同
Our DNA is identical.
他说的是事实
He's telling you the truth.
闭嘴
Shut up.
他选择我是因为没人能超越我
He chose me 'cause there's never been anybody like me,
他知道我总有一天会变老  那时就用上你了
and he knew one day I was gonna get old and then you'd step in.
他一直在骗你
He's been lying to you the whole time.
他跟你说你是孤儿
He told you you were an orphan.
全世界那么多人追杀我
And of all the people in the world to come after me,
为什么他派你来
why would he send you?
因为我是最厉害的
Because I'm the best.
你显然不是最厉害的
You are obviously not the best.
你真是死脑子
You got a hard-ass head.
估计这应该是你生日什么的
Guess this was supposed to be your birthday or something.
我必须死  必须你动手
I had to die, and you had to do it.
只要我还活着
As long as I was alive,
克雷的小实验就不算完成
somehow Clay's little experiment was incomplete.
你就是在为那个疯子杀人
That's the maniac you're pulling a trigger for.
你别跟我说他
Shut your mouth about him.
你只是想让我慌乱
You're just trying to rattle me.
我是想救你
I'm trying to save you!
你二十三岁了吧
What are you, 23?
还是处男吧
Still a virgin, right?
看来没错
Yeah.
渴望谈恋爱与人相通
Dying to be in a relationship and connect,
却又害怕让任何人靠近
but terrified to let anybody near you.
因为万一有人看清你的真面目呢
Because what if somebody actually saw who you are?
他们怎么可能爱你
How could they love you?
所以每个人都只是目标
So everybody's just targets,
你就只是武器
and you're just a weapon.
别开枪
Don't shoot him!
不  不要
Don't! No!
放下
Drop it!
放下  不然我开枪了
Drop it! I will shoot you!
不  你不会的
No, you won't!
放开他
Get your hands off of him!
Let him go!
马上
Right now!
我不是你
I'm not you!
听到了吗  老头
You hear me, old man?
我不是你
I'm not you!
-他在哪  -他走了
- Where is he? - He's gone.
-你打中他了吗  -应该是
- Did you hit him? - I think so, yeah.
-打哪了  -好像是肩膀
- Where? - Shoulder, I think.
那他就能恢复
Then he'll recover.
算是好事吗
Is that a good thing?
要知道  目睹一个人
You know, it's not every day you see
在两大洲上被自己胖揍
a guy get his ass kicked on two continents
可不常见
by himself.
去哪
Where to?
乔治亚州
Georgia.
威利斯在那儿
It's where Verris is.
天啊
Man.
可怜的孩子
That poor kid.
他一定吓坏了
He must be terrified.
而回家后等着他的更可怕
And he's going home, walking into a buzz saw.
我得睡一会儿了
I need to get some sleep.
你也是
You too.
我不睡  梦里有鬼魂
Not me. That's where the ghosts are.
睡吧
Sleep.
跟我说说
Tell me something.
为什么杀这个人对你这么难
Why is it so hard for you to kill this man?
你知道我多讨厌大吊床公园吗  老爹
You know how much I hate Big Hammock Park, Pop?
什么
What?
从十二岁开始
Ever since I was about 12 years old...
每次过生日都去那打火鸡
we would shoot turkeys there for my birthday.
我一直都很讨厌
And I always hated it.
可我是个孤儿  对吗
But I was an orphan, right?
那是怎么知道我生日是哪天的呢
So, how would we even know when my birthday was?
可你似乎从未察觉  所以就一直去那儿
But you never seemed to notice, so we just keep going.
好吧  明年生日去吃查克奶酪
Okay, so, next year we'll try Chuck E. Cheese.
好
Yeah.
你  我
You, me,
还有实验室把我造出来的那帮人
and the lab guys who made me.
对
Yeah.
我
I, um...
一直认为
always believed...
不让你知道你会更快乐
you'd be happier not knowing.
快乐
Happy.
你知道我什么时候快乐吗  老爹
You know when I'm happy, Pop?
当我趴在地上
When I'm flat on my belly,
即将扣动扳机的那一刻
about to squeeze a trigger.
那是我唯一快乐的时候
It's the only time I'm happy.
这都算不上什么失误
And this wasn't even a mistake.
这和你把别人肚子搞大
It's not like you got someone pregnant
不得不负起责任抚养我不一样
and then had to man up and raise me.
是你  做出了决定
No, you made a decision
让科学家用一个人造出另一个人
to have a scientist make a person out of another person.
不  事情不是这样的
No, that's not what it was.
就是这么回事
That's exactly what it was.
然后你派我
Then you sent me...
去杀他
to kill him.
全世界那么多枪手
Of all the shooters in the world,
为什么偏偏派我
why would you send me?
他是你的黑暗  你得靠自己走过去
He's your darkness. You had to walk through this on your own.
也许你才是我的黑暗
Maybe you're my darkness.
你跟我说的谎
That lie you told me...
说我父母
that my parents...
把我遗弃在消防站
dumped me at a fire station.
我相信了
And I believed that.
你知道那让我有什么感觉吗
Do you know how that made me feel?
那是不得已的谎言
It was a necessary lie.
这一切都没有什么不得已
None of this shit is necessary!
你选择了这样对我
You made a choice to do this to me.
你看不出来我有多难过吗
Can't you see how not okay I am?
胡说
Bullshit!
你忘了自己是在跟谁说话  小克
You forget who you're talking to, Junior.
我上过战场
I've seen battle.
我见过士兵
I've seen soldiers
因为对他们的要求超出了他们的能力而崩溃
go over the edge because more was being asked of them than they could give.
但你不会
That's not you.
你的世界既稳定又可靠
Your world is stable and dependable.
我保证了这一点
I made sure of that.
你有亨利从来都没有的东西
You have something that Henry himself never had.
你有一个慈爱  无私  顾家的父亲
You have a loving, dedicated, present father,
每一天都告诉你
who tells you every goddamn day
你有多宝贵  多重要
that you are precious and that you matter.
这件事的意义就在于
Jesus, the whole point of this thing
去除亨利的痛苦  把他全部的天赋
was to give you all of Henry's gifts
都给你  而且我做到了
without his pain, and I did.
不要怀疑  小克
Don't doubt, Junior.
你能做得更好
You're better than that.
过来
Come here.
我爱你  儿子
I love you, son.
别让自己失望
Just don't let yourself down.
就像我的许多艳遇一样
Like so many of my encounters,
短暂而甜蜜
it was short but sweet.
谢谢  宝贝
Thanks, baby.
这边应该有辆卡车
There should be a truck here somewhere.
别动
Don't move.
子弹里面是什么
What was in that?
蜂毒
Bee venom.
不  不  你不能这样
No. No, you can't do that.
你不能这么做  他过敏
You can't do that. He's allergic!
亨利  你能呼吸吗
Henry, can you breathe?
亨利  试着呼吸
Henry, try to breathe.
-你没事吧  -拜托
- You okay? - Please.
亨利  亨利  你能呼吸吗
Henry. Henry, can you breathe?
求你了
Please!
用力呼吸  亨利  亨利
Try to breathe. Henry! Henry!
呼吸
Breathe!
-你为什么这么做  -加油  亨利
- Why are you doing this? - Come on, Henry.
-你为什么这么做  -亨利  亨利  呼吸
- Why are you doing this? - Henry. Henry, breathe. Come on!
呼吸  亨利
Breathe, Henry.
肾上腺素抗组胺剂
Epinephrine antihistamine.
你会没事的
You'll be fine.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我得确认一下
I had to be sure.
不用  没事
No, it's all good.
这破事是挺难让人接受的
This whole shit's been a little difficult.
不好意思插个话
I hate to break up the party,
你为什么总能知道我们在哪
but how the hell do you always know where we are?
他们在追踪你
They're tracking you.
你相信我吗
Do you trust me?
三年前做手术时  他们给你安了芯片
They chipped you... during your surgery three years ago.
威利斯
Verris.
你也认识他
You know him too?
巴拿马  科威特  索马里
Panama. Kuwait. Somalia.
你能带我们去找他吗
Can you take us to him?
我们得阻止他
We need to shut him down.
我们两个一起
Both of us.
你在费城长大的吧
You grew up in Philadelphia, right?
对  在一个叫"底部"的地方
Yep. Place called "The Bottom."
底部
The Bottom.
给我讲讲我母亲
Tell me about my mother.
海伦·杰克逊·布罗根
Helen Jackson Brogan.
做两份工作  做了四十年
Worked two jobs for 40 years.
以前总打我屁股
That woman used to whup my ass.
-是不是该打  -通常是
- Did you deserve it? - Usually.
臭脾气还特别蠢
Does being angry and stupid
什么事都不上心是不是该打
and never really trying at anything mean you deserve it?
我们的父亲不常在家
Our father wasn't around much.
我五岁的时候他就离开了
He left when I was five.
我觉得她每次看到我就仿佛看到了他
And I think every time she looked at me, she just saw him, so...
我必须离开那里
I had to get the hell out of there.
参了军
Joined the corps.
第一次结交了真正的朋友
First time I ever made any real friends.
陆战队
Oorah.
在那认识了克雷·威利斯
Met Clay Verris there.
发现了自己特别特别擅长的事
Found something I was really, really good at.
退役的时候  勋章挂满了前胸
Time I left, I had medals on my chest,
她已经去世了  我成了这个样子
she was gone, and... I had become this.
你得趁还能脱身的时候尽早脱身
You gotta walk away while you still can.
-我只会这些  -不  他只教了你这些
- This is all I know. - No, this is all he taught you.
现在收手  你还能有别的作为
Stop now, you can still become something else.
行啊
Sure.
医生  律师
A doctor? Lawyer?
丈夫  父亲
Husband. Father.
所有这份工作让你能逃避的事
All the things this job gives you the excuse not to be.
我把那些都抛弃了
I threw all of that away.
第二次机会再浪费这些天赋就太可惜了
It'd be a shame to waste these gifts a second time around.
抱歉  你叫什么名字
I'm sorry, what is your name?
一直都叫我小克
It's always been Junior.
小克雷
Clay Junior.
我也不知道自己是谁了
I don't really know anymore.
又一个退出的好理由
That's another really good reason to quit.
你确定要这样吗
You sure about this?
我得跟他谈谈
I need to talk to him.
我们见到他之后要怎么办
So, what happens when we get to him?
他是不会投降的
He's not gonna surrender.
是他
It's him.
我能跟他通话吗
Can I talk to him?
我想亲口告诉他我们现在是死党了
I want to be the one to tell him we're all BFFs now.
接吧
Take it.
我是小克
This is Junior.
你和布罗根在一起吗
Are you with Brogan?
我为什么要跟他在一起  你不是派我去杀他吗
Why would I be with him? You sent me to kill him, didn't you?
不重要了  快跑
Doesn't matter. Just run.
什么
What?
跑  离他远点  快
Run. Get away from him, now.
小克  我只想让你安全无事
Junior, I just want you safe.
为什么
Why?
因为我是你最爱的实验品
Because I'm your favorite experiment?
不  因为我是你父亲  你要听我的
No, because I'm your father and you need to listen to me.
快跑
Run!
-下车  -快  快
- Get out of the car! - Go, go!
巴伦
Baron!
不
No!
快走
Come on!
很遗憾  亨利
I'm sorry, Henry.
下车  快  快
Move out. Go! Go!
-米切尔队长  -请讲
- Chief Mitchell? - Go ahead.
我是克雷·威利斯  我要你的小队撤退
Clay Verris. I need your units to stand down.
长官
Sir?
我们正在对付一个
We're engaging with a terror cell
拥有生物武器的恐怖组织
that has a weaponized biological capability.
各单位  立即撤退
All units, fall back immediately.
已经通知联邦当局  他们正在路上
Federal authorities have been notified and are en route.
收到  保持联络  克雷
Affirmative. Keep me posted, Clay.
好的  长官
Yes, sir.
你得让手下的人撤退
You gotta stand your men down now.
小克  你做了正确选择  离开了他
You did the right thing, Junior, walking away from him.
我做了懦夫做的事
I did what a coward would do.
让我恶心
Makes me sick!
我对你要求过高了
I was asking too much of you.
我现在明白了
I can see that now.
他不该在车上被导弹炸死  老爹
He deserves better than a missile shot into his car, Pop.
他怎么死不重要
It doesn't matter what he deserves.
他必须死
He has to die.
现在你可以命令那些杀手撤退了吗
Are you gonna call those goons off now?
不  但你可以
No. But you can.
只要开枪  接管指挥
Just fire that. Take command.
装甲的弱点在接缝处
Armor is weak at the joints.
击中眼睛和脖子最致命
Eyes and neck are the kill shots.
你负责右边  我负责左边
Take right, I take left.
记住枪战准则
Muzzle discipline.
注意还剩几发子弹  你装子弹  我进攻
Watch your round count. You set, I spike.
-准备好了吗  -了解
- Ready? - Roger that.
-没子弹了  -找掩护
- I'm out. - Take cover.
装好了
Set!
扔手雷
Frag out!
我是想让你成为男子汉
I am trying to make you a man!
我该克隆我自己的
I should've cloned myself.
"慈爱  无私  顾家的父亲"
"Loving, dedicated, present father."
右边
Right side!
来吧
Go ahead.
动手
Do it.
你还剩多少子弹
How many rounds you got left?
一发
One.
好吧
Okay.
对不起
I'm sorry.
为什么
For what?
把你卷进这事
For getting you into this.
是我先监视你的
I was the one surveilling you.
是啊
Yeah.
不过还是对不起
Anyway, sorry.
现在一起杀出去吧
Now let's fight our way out of this thing.
你是个很棒的搭档
You're a great partner.
谢谢
Thank you.
抱歉我跑掉了
Sorry I ran.
没关系  今晚战局混乱
Yeah, well, it's been a rough night.
外面还有多少人
How many more out there?
我看没有了
I didn't see any.
威利斯呢
Verris?
昏迷了
Out of commission.
但还活着吗
But still alive?
对
Yes.
给你
Here.
伤势严重吗
How bad is that?
我没事
I'm fine.
你有事
You're not.
在高处守着  我们得保住出口
Hold the elevated position. We're gonna secure an out.
退后
Back off!
你感觉不到痛吗
Don't you feel pain?
我不知道你为何如此生气  亨利
I don't know why you're so angry, Henry.
这一切的灵感都源于你
You were the inspiration for all of this.
你知道我怎么想到的吗  你还好吗
You know where I got the idea? Are you okay?
卡夫奇
Khafji.
看着你挨家挨户地战斗
Watching you go house to house,
真希望我能有一支精锐部队
wishing I had a whole division of men
都和你一样优秀
all as good as you.
我想看看这能不能实现
Wondering if that could be possible.
你该感到荣幸
You should be flattered.
你该去死
You should be dead.
你看见当时的情景了
You saw what happened over there.
血腥暴行
Atrocities.
用棺材把朋友们送回家
Friends being sent home in a pine box.
如果有更好的出路  我们为什么要接受那一切
Why should we accept that if there's a better way?
看看我们创造了什么
And look what we created.
他身上有你和我的影子
He's got both of us in him.
你不觉得祖国值得拥有一个完美版的你吗
Don't you think your country deserves a perfect version of you?
没有什么完美版的我
There is no perfect version of me.
完美版的他  或是任何人
Or him. Or anybody.
没有吗
No?
他本该前往也门
He was on his way to Yemen.
现在拜你所赐  某对父母的孩子
Now, thanks to you, his place is gonna be taken
将代替他征战
by someone with parents.
这个人能感受到痛苦和恐惧
Someone who feels pain, fear,
而我们去除了他的这些知觉
which we had edited out of him.
这个人身上的弱点
Someone with just as many weaknesses
和我们要杀戮的恐怖分子一样多
as the terrorists that we're trying to kill.
你要告诉我这样更好吗
And you're gonna tell me that's better?
那干脆造出一整支军队吧
So why not make a whole army of them?
对  为什么不呢
Yeah. Why not?
想想我们能让多少美国家庭免于参战
Think how many American families we could spare.
不用再牺牲谁家的儿子或女儿
Nobody's son or daughter would ever have to die.
不会再有老兵退役回乡  患上创伤后应激障碍再自杀
No vet comes home with PTSD and kills himself.
我们保卫世界安全  也不会带来现实中的不幸
We can keep the whole world safe without any actual grief.
所以...我伤害了谁
So... who would I be hurting?
你谈论的可是人  克雷
You're talking about people, Clay.
亨利
Henry.
这是双子做过的最人道的事
This is the most humane thing that Gemini's ever done.
还有多少跟我一样的人
How many more of me are running around out there?
只有一个你  小克
There's only one you, Junior.
他只是个武器
He was a weapon.
你是我儿子
You're my son.
我爱你
And I love you...
跟所有爱孩子的父亲一样
as much as any father ever loved any kid.
我没有父亲
I don't have a father.
再见  克雷
Goodbye, Clay.
那我们要怎么做
So what the hell are we gonna do, huh?
将他归罪  他不会受到审讯
Gonna turn him in? They're not gonna try him.
他们不会关掉他的实验室
They're not gonna shut down his lab.
我们现在得了结这一切
We have to end this right now.
看着我
Look at me.
你扣下扳机
You pull that trigger,
就会破坏你内心的一部分
and you're gonna break something inside of yourself...
再也无法愈合
that'll never get fixed again.
不要
Don't.
放手吧
Let it go.
把枪给我
Give it to me.
你可不想被鬼魂缠上
You don't want those ghosts.
相信我
Trust me.
你知道不该喝酒的
You should know better than that.
很惊讶你还在乎
Surprised you give a shit.
我们不能做朋友了
Well, we can't be friends anymore.
因为你没阻止他们杀我
Because you did let them try to kill me.
但不意味着我想看到你把自己喝死
But doesn't mean I want to see you drink yourself to death.
双子实验室被拆了
The Gemini lab's been dismantled.
克隆项目已成历史
Cloning program is history.
那小克呢
And Junior?
没人能动他
He's untouchable.
再也不会有人去打扰他
No one will bother him, ever.
我们查过了  没有其他克隆人了
And we checked, there are no more clones.
那你呢
What about you?
检察长来电了
IG called.
我要被起诉了
I'm looking at charges,
但如果我供出简妮特  就能争取脱罪
but if I bury Janet, I can make a deal.
她活该
Well, she earned it.
我真的很抱歉  亨利
I'm really sorry, Henry.
保重  德尔
Take care, Del.
你也是
Yeah, you too.
祝你退休愉快
And happy retirement.
六个月后
很高兴见到你
Good to see you.
恭喜升职
Congrats on the promotion.
我听说他们制定了宏大计划
I hear they got big plans.
和你经历过这段  没什么是我不能搞定的
Well, after you, pretty sure I can handle anything.
-你过得怎么样  -很好
- How have you been? - Good.
我刚处理完巴伦的后事
I just, uh, settled Baron's estate,
把他的骨灰撒在了加勒比海
scattered his ashes in the Caribbean.
我不知道  现在我只想
I don't know. All I want to do now is
为世界做点贡献
put some good in the world.
我只是要找到方法
I just got to figure out how.
你会找到的
Yeah, you will.
你睡得还好吗
You, uh, sleeping okay?
好些了
Better.
-没有鬼魂了  -不像以前那样了
- No ghosts? - Not like before.
还有前几天我居然照镜子了
And I actually looked in a mirror the other day.
-真的吗  -没什么可怕的
- Really? - It wasn't horrendous.
说到镜子...
Speaking of mirrors...
-待会儿见  -待会儿见
- Catch you later. - See you later, man.
这是什么
What's this?
这是你
This is you.
护照
护照  出生证明  驾照
Passport, birth certificate, driver's license.
显然你的信用记录不错
Apparently you got pretty good credit.
我喜欢你选的这个名字
I love the name you chose.
杰克逊  这是我母亲的名字
Jackson? It was my mother's name.
她先是我的母亲
She was my mother first.
是啊  是啊
Yeah, yeah.
别敷衍我  年轻人
Don't you "Yeah, yeah" me, young man.
走吧  我知道一家吃午饭的好餐厅
Come on. I know a great place for lunch.
你选定专业了吗
So you settled on a major yet?
倾向于选工程学
Leaning towards engineering.
工程学
Engineering?
对  你该听她的
Yeah, you should listen to her.
我要是你
If I were you,
在某种意义上我就是你
which I sort of am,
我会学计算机科学
I'd go with computer science.
那是读研究生的事了  你该从人文学科起步
Save that for grad school. You want to start in humanities.
-好吧  还是别听她的  -别听他的才对
- Okay, don't listen to her. - Don't listen to him.
你需要学习经典打基础
You need a grounding in the classics.
不好意思  我在跟我自己讨论呢
Look, excuse me, I'm trying to talk with myself here.
对  你在自说自话  而不是对他说话
Yeah. You're talking to yourself, but you're not talking to him.
我年轻时犯过很多错
Look, I just made a lot of mistakes when I was young--
实际上  有些错误我想自己去经历
And I'd actually like to make some of those mistakes myself.
我想说的是
What I'm trying to say is,
你不必重蹈我的覆辙
I made them already so you don't have to.
但他不是你
Yeah, but he's not you.
好了二位  冷静冷静
Okay. Everybody, chill the hell out.
我会没事的
I'm gonna be okay.
你没事
If you're okay...
我就没事
I'm okay.
怎么了
What?
我只是不敢相信三十年后
I just can't believe that in 30 years,
我会长成你这样
I'm gonna look like you.
什么  拜托  你倒想呢
What? Please. You wish.
小子  你最好祈祷三十年后能跟我一样
Boy, you better hope you look like me in 30 years.
站在你面前的是
This is 50-year-old,
五十岁的成熟猛男
mature man meat you're looking at.
是五十一岁
Fifty-one.
我认真刷牙  用牙线  我努力工作
I brush. I floss. I work hard.
等你到了五十岁  我打赌你不会
When you're 50, I bet you won't be dragging your ass
像我一样每天早上爬起来跑步
around the track every morning like I do.
其实我们现在就可以赛跑
In fact, we can race now.
马上就跑  现在就跑去那个拐角
We can race right now. We'll take it to the corner right now.